Thad, we've covered a lot of different machine learning algorithms.
Thad 我们已经学习了许多不同的机器学习算法
But what about situations where we have time series?
但是包含时间序列的情况是什么呢？
&gt;&gt; You mean like speech recognition?
— 你是说语音识别之类的吗？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I know you've worked in sign language recognition and
— 对 我知道你已经研究了手语识别
handwriting recognition.
和手写识别
They seem to be similar problems.
它们看起来是类似的问题
&gt;&gt; Yep, they are.
— 没错 的确是这样
Pattern recognition through time is one of my specialties.
通过时间的模式识别是我的专业之一
And it's where the AI community has made a lot of progress.
这也是人工智能业界获得巨大进步的领域
When you think about it, pattern recognition through time should be
想想吧 通过时间的模式识别应该
easier than situations where you have just one measurement.
比你只有一种测量的情景更加简单
&gt;&gt; You mean like how face recognition is easier when you have a video of
— 你的意思是有某个人的视频
a person, as opposed to a single photo?
要比只有他的照片时 人脸识别更加容易吗？
If one particular frame of the video is badly lit or
如果视频中某一帧灯光昏暗或者他扭头看到别处
the person is looking away the next frame might be better.
可能下一帧会好很多
&gt;&gt; Precisely.
— 没错
But in this section, we are going to focus on situations where there's
但是在这部分我们要关注
a language-like structure to the problem.
包含语言形式结构问题的情景
In other words, there's some fundamental unit, like a phoning in speech, or
换句话说 其中有些基础单元 例如语音电话
letter in handwriting,
或手写的信
that's combined with other units to make bigger constructs like words.
与其他单元一起形成了更宏大的结构 如词语
Which are then combined in even larger structures, like sentences.
这些词汇然后形成了更大的结构 如语句
&gt;&gt; So besides speech, sign language and handwriting,
— 除了语音 手语和手写形式
what other problems have the same sort of structure?
其他哪些问题也有相同的结构呢？
&gt;&gt; Well, in my opinion,
— 在我看来
most human activities through time have a language-like structure.
通过时间的大多数人类活动都具有语言结构
Playing basketball, driving a car, or
打篮球 开汽车
even just vacuuming the floor, all seem to have similiar units of movement,
或者用真空吸尘器清扫地板 所有看起来都有类似的动作单元
combinations of those movements and source statistical grammar.
运动组合和这样的统计语法
I believe this area of AI is one of the most promising for future research.
我认为人工智能这一领域是未来研究中最有潜力的部分
I'm excited to share my knowledge of the subject.
我非常高兴分享这个话题的知识
&gt;&gt; And then we're going to cover dynamic time warp and
— 接下来我们就在这一部分学习动态时间规整
hidden Markov models in this section.
和隐马尔可夫模型吧
Where should we start?
我们应该从哪里开始呢？
&gt;&gt; Well, let's start with a challenge question on HMMs that gives a preview of
— 我们首先从隐马尔可夫模型的挑战问题开始
what we're going to be learning. 最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6
这可以让我们初步了解将要学习的内容. 最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6